

Front-End Developer

- ⊕ huseyn-ismayilov.vercel.app
- <u>i.huseynn0@gmail.com</u>
- **(**+994) 50 978 68 52
- Azerbaijan, Baku

SUMMARY

I am an accomplished front-end developer with a rich background in web development. Close to 3 years of hands-on experience, I have successfully collaborated with diverse clients as a seasoned freelancer. My proficiency extends across the spectrum of web development and design, where I have honed my skills in creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Front-End developer, Bionuk

bionluk.com/cyweb

Dec 2021 - Present

- · More than 150 satisfied customers in total
- I developed UI/UX (mostly Figma and XD) designs as pixel perfect into user-friendly web interfaces.
- Successfully completed projects by communicating effectively with customers and the design team.
- Created web sites that are mobile friendly and responsive to various screen sizes.

Ceo & Web Developer, Cyweb Agency

cywebagency.com

Aug 2021 - May 2023

- Developed many corporate and e-commerce sites with wordpress.
- UI/UX designs were developed with Elementor in WordPress

SKILLS



EDUCATION

Duzce University

Political Science and Public Administration

Mart 2021 - May 2023

CERTIFICATES

FreeCodeCamp - Front End Development Libraries

IBM - Intermediate Web and Front-End Development

Codecademy - React Course

Jed Academy - Front-End Developer

LANGUAGES

English: B1 | Turkish: C1 | Azerbaijan: Native

LINKS

Github https://github.com/Huseyn-Ismayilov/

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/huseyn-ismayilov-980aab201

Instagram https://www.instagram.com/thehuseyn0/